[Music]
today's Monday makeup lesson is a
daytime smokey eye any colors can be
used to create the smokey eye you just
need three shades of a similar tone step
one prime your eyelids this will help
the eyeshadows last all
[Music]
day step two taking a blending brush and
a matte medium toned eyeshadow apply
this into the crease
[Music]
take your time blending this softly
towards the
[Music]
Brows step three with a similar
eyeshadow apply this to the rest of the
eyelid
making sure to connect right at the
crease step four apply your darkest
eyeshadow at the base of the lashes and
softly blend this up towards the middle
of the eyelid
[Music]
step five curl your eyelashes and apply
plenty of
[Music]
mascara and you're done it's super easy
and I hope you guys try this out